We were abandoned.
That's why we live in a camp
surrounded by walls.
Because the blood of devils
runs through us.
That's also why your father isn't here.
Your father... is Marleyan.
He can't be with us Eldians.
If only we were Marleyan...
Oh, yeah...
Back then, I strove to be a Warrior
so we could be Marleyans.
Who said you could walk?!
Run, you filthy seed of swine!
Don't you wanna be Honorary Marleyans?!
Did you guys hear? We're attacking
Paradis Island in just a few years.
Huh?
It's almost time for us to inherit Titans!
Out of the seven of us, they're picking six!
Yes! I can finally be Marleyan!
Huh? Why so excited?
If anyone's the worst, it's you.
Excuse me?!
What's your strong point?
Huh?
Your strength? Your brains?
Your aim? Combat ability?
Nope. The only value they see in you
is your loyalty to Marley.
"I'll slaughter the island devils
real good for you, sir!"
You making fun of our mission?!
Or maybe you're a stray Restorationist?!
Huh?!
You are, aren't you?!
I'll report you to the commander!
Report this, you little shit!
Want some more?!
Porco, enough!
Hating the island doesn't make you special!
Have fun waiting 13 years alone!
--Tsk!
--Porco!
Let's go, Pieck.
Don't cry too long or the
commander will chew me out.
Reiner, I'm sorry.
Stand up, Reiner.
C'mon.
I'm gonna become a Marleyan
and live with my mom and dad.
I can't wait 13 years.
But it's like he said. I'm the worst.
Porco doesn't make the decision.
Besides, loyalty is important.
Right, Annie?
Huh? What? I wasn't listening.
You really want that as your goal?
Huh?
Thirteen years is all you get.
Thirteen years to be a hero.
If I crush the devils on Paradis,
I'll save the world.
Then my parents will be proud
to have me as a son.
I wish something would happen.
Eren! There you are!
"The Door of Hope"
Marvelous. Even better than we expected.
The Female Titan.
Versatility is its biggest strength.
On top of its mobility and endurance,
its hardened strikes are incredibly destructive.
The range is limited,
but it can call Pure Titans, too.
Leonhart is perfect.
The Armored Titan specializes in hardening.
If it charges in at full speed,
the gates of any wall will crumble.
As Marley's shield that must withstand attacks,
it suits Braun's perseverance.
The Jaw Titan is an assault weapon.
It's as speedy as it is small, with claws
and jaw that crush nearly everything.
Entrusted to the quick-witted Marcel.
The Beast Titan is as potent as ever.
Though slightly larger than the other Titans,
its throwing technique is dreadful
on another level.
What's more, his blood
seems to have hidden power.
The Cart Titan has outstanding endurance,
suitable for long missions.
It can be outfitted with different
equipment to extend its usefulness.
Pieck's superior judgment will serve well.
And then, there's the Colossal Titan...
A god of destruction.
Hoover will be able to handle it.
I feel bad for those island devils.
One day, that's gonna show up to kill 'em.
This new Warrior unit may
outperform their predecessors,
but I question the military's decision.
Sending children to retake the
Founding Titan sounds insane to me.
You think? Didn't those children
just crush a nation before our eyes?
It's messed up! Why was
the worst of us chosen?!
What did you do?!
Seems you're the worst.
That's all there is to it, Pock.
You little--!
Porco! You sure you wanna defy the brass?!
Huh?
Reiner... I'm sorry.
Dad!
It's you, right? Mom used to work in
these barracks before I was born!
That's where you met her! Karina Braun!
Look at this! Mom and I are
Honorary Marleyans! We can all live--
Bloody hell!
Did that woman send you here?!
To get revenge on me?! Shit!
Now her kid's a Warrior?!
If they find out where you're from,
my family is screwed!
You're gonna get me hanged!
I'm running the hell away!
Away from you and your damn Eldian mother!
Reiner!
I'll be waiting for you!
That's right. Even without a father,
I'm still the chosen Warrior
of the Armored Titan.
I'll save everyone from the island devils
and be the world's hero.
We didn't cover much ground tonight.
Can't do much about the clouds.
Will the King really not use the Founding
Titan, even if we break the wall?
What's the use asking now?
Trust Marley's research.
That's right. We can't turn back.
Tomorrow, we reach the wall... and then...
Huh? What? Are you having second
thoughts about killing the devils?
Have you forgotten what they've done?
We're the world's chosen Warriors
sent to punish the island devils!
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Reiner, I'm sorry. You were never meant
to be chosen as a Warrior.
I talked you up and criticized
my brother to influence their decision.
Huh?
I... just wanted to protect my brother.
I'm sorry, Reiner... I'm sorry!
Why... are you apologizing?
Bertholdt...! Annie...! Marcel...!
They got eaten!
They got eaten because of me!
And I'll be next!
This is where I'm gonna die!
Not bad.
This is a first. You actually beat me...
in a long-distance... race...
Huh?
If we... took out that Titan...
we wouldn't have... lost Jaw...
Shit! Now Marcel's gone for good.
They said there wouldn't be Titans this far out!
We've gotta go home.
Huh?
Let's find Jaw and leave.
They would've changed back to human.
Besides, without Marcel to lead,
this mission is doomed.
Wait...
We can't...
We can't!
We can't go home!
We've gotta continue the mission!
Oh, yeah... If we go back now,
you'll just get eaten by the next Warrior.
Not that I give a shit.
You think only I will?
Huh?
That only I'll get the blame for running away?
You guys are that certain
you won't get eaten, too?
Catching Jaw won't be easy either.
If they used its power and ran,
our Titans could never catch up.
They can't control it right after becoming--
You controlled the Colossal Titan, no problem!
Anyways, we're doomed at this rate!
Without the Founding Titan,
there's no going home!
Back there, if you were a fraction
as calm as you are now,
we wouldn't have lost Marcel or Jaw.
But you've got no problem intimidating
us to save your own ass, huh?!
How about you come clean to Magath?!
Tell him, "It's all my fault!"
Honorary Marleyan, my ass!
Chosen Warrior, my ass!
Marleyans, Eldians! They're all liars!
Everyone only thinks about themselves!
I'm no different! I've gotta get home alive!
If you feel guilty, just die!
Take all the blame and die!
Reiner is dead.
If we need Marcel, then I'll be Marcel.
Please, stop this...
This is the only way we'll be able
to go back home!
Let's go back... together... to our hometown!
Huh?
I wanted to be a Warrior.
I thought I could make my mom's wish
come true and we'd live with my father.
But... I had a father who
didn't want any part of us.
My mom had a dream she knew
would never come true.
I should never have been chosen.
I should have died today.
Why'd he apologize?
Why'd he save someone like me?
No! I'm not ready for this to end!
I still don't understand anything!
Where is this?
Inside Wall Rose.
Annie... Bertholdt...
I'm sorry.
Marcel... I'll be the Warrior I should've been.
You! What the hell did you come here for?!
To save humanity!
"Information Available for Public Disclosure"
"Warrior Candidates"
"A unit of child soldiers consisting of Eldian 'devils.' Under command of the Marley army, they undergo harsh training and are selected based on their grades, skills, behavior, personality, and devotion to Marley.
As only Eldian 'devils' can inherit the Nine Titans,
the existence of Eldians is crucial for the
defense of Marley. As such, Eldians selected to become Warriors are granted 'Honorary Marleyan' status along with their immediate family."
I lived in Wall Maria,
deep in the southeast mountains.
It happened at dawn.
The animals were all stirred up
and I heard a strange rumbling.
Thinking it was footsteps,
I opened the window...
The rest is a blur,
but I ran away on my horse.
Leaving behind three kids
about the same age as you guys.
Hey, missy. You've got good taste
in men to tail a geezer like me.
I was born at an inn.
My mom, who works there, talks about
my father so much, I know that it's you.
Well, that's real touching. If you want
a hug from papa, put your hands up.
How are you sure it's not you?
I made a promise to my sister.
This joke of yours ain't making me laugh.
You're so mean, papa!
Hey now... Having a rebellious phase, are we?
That's a new one.
Are his legs saying snow today?
Nah. That's the clear skies position.
Call it hail or you'll be late for muster.
Wake up, Bertholdt!
While you two snoozed
after playing with your friends,
I was busy crawling around
the capital's sewers.
I've hit my limit if he's around.
Your limit, huh?
Let's take what we know back to Marley.
They'll be happy to hear anything.
Do you honestly think that?
Not if it's all we have to show
after five years.
Then, what are you saying we do?!
Destroy Wall Rose.
It's the only way we can
smoke out the Founding Titan.
A lot of your friends are gonna die.
I keep telling you:
They're not friends--they're devils.
But gaining their trust can't hurt.
And frankly, your aloof behavior isn't--
I'm gonna barf. Can you move
your face away from mine?
I bet you're exhausted.
Sorry for always laying the burden on you.
Let's call it a day.
I keep having the same dream.
I dream about the guy
who hung himself in the fields.
Why did he tell us that story
right before he hung himself?
Eren, take a break. You're gonna die.
Shit!
Reiner... How do you do it?
How can I get like you and Mikasa?
At this rate, I'll die without
doing a damn thing!
Just do what you've gotta do.
Keep moving forward.
That's all we can do.
Yeah. You're right.
Aren't you gonna drive out every last Titan?
I know you can do it.
Shit! I can't let this go on!
That's right... I still have those guys...
The hospital...
Hey!
Um, I guess you're recovering well.
You're good enough to talk now.
Kinda. I'm here for
emotional trauma, but it's a lie.
Huh?
I said I lost my memory and can't
go home, but I just don't want to.
It'd be hard to face my family now.
Will you snitch on me?
I wouldn't do that.
You're hurt. Is it from your Warrior training?
Yeah, but I won't become one.
Another candidate is so talented,
I don't even stand a chance.
That's good to hear.
Huh?
You're a good guy. I hope you live a long life.
But I don't want them to be a Warrior.
Why not?
Is the other candidate a girl?
She's famous around here.
She did incredible things in the war.
Everyone's saying she should
be the next Armor.
But since I'm powerless,
I can't do a damn thing about it.
Every day I'm here, I think:
Why did it ever come to this?
Damaged minds and bodies...
Their freedom taken away...
Even losing themselves.
If people knew it would come to this,
nobody would go to war.
But most people are pushed by something,
forced to march into hell.
That "something" wasn't their choice.
Their situation or others made them do it.
But people who push their own backs
see a different kind of hell.
They can see something beyond the hell.
It might be hope.
It may even be another hell.
Only those who keep moving
forward will ever know.
Magath sorts out the military
for the Tybur family to tell the truth.
As the festival enlivens the city,
an unexpected surprise awaits Reiner.
Next episode: "From One Hand to Another."
"From One Hand to Another"